durect.com 2007-07-30

# DURECT: Privacy Policy

Welcome to www.durect.com. This site is owned by DURECT Corporation. Privacy is very important to us. We also understand that privacy is very important to you. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding collection, use and disclosure of information that you may provide via this site. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information to this site. DURECT and its affiliates also operate other web sites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the other DURECT web sites. You should review the privacy statement posted on other DURECT web sites when you visit them. This site is intended for use by residents of the United States.

**Your Consent**  
By using this site, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**About Children**  
This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect information from site visitors in this age group.

**Active Information Collection**  
Like many Web sites, this site actively collects information from its visitors both by asking you specific questions and by permitting you to communicate directly with us via e-mail. Some of the information that you submit may be personally identifiable information (that is, information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your full name, address, e-mail address, phone number and so on).

Some areas of this site may require you to submit information in order for you to benefit from the specified features (such as email alerts, requests for information packages or webcast attendance forms through the investor relations site). You will be informed at each information collection point what information is required and what information is optional.

**Passive Information Collection**  
As you navigate through a Web site, certain information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without you actively providing the information) using various technologies and means, such as Internet Protocol addresses, cookies, Internet tags, and navigational data collection. This site may use Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP Address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider so you can access the Internet and is generally considered to be non-personally identifiable information, because in most cases and IP address is dynamic (changing each time you connect to the Internet), rather than static (unique to a particular user's computer). We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our server, report aggregate information, determine the fastest route for your computer to use in connecting to our site, and administer and improve the site.

A "cookie" is a bit of information that a Web site sends to your Web browser that helps the site remember information about you and your preferences.

"Session" cookies are temporary bits of information that are erased once you exit your Web browsers window or otherwise turn your computer off. Session cookies are used to improve navigation on Web sites and to collect aggregate statistical information. This site uses session cookies.

"Persistent" cookies are more permanent bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of your computer and stay there unless you delete the cookie. Persistent cookies store information on your computer for a number of purposes, such as retrieving certain information you may have previously provided (e.g. passwords) and helping to determine what areas of the Web site visitors find most valuable. This site uses persistent cookies.

"Navigational data" ("log files," and "server logs") are used for system management to improve the content of the site, market research purposes, and to communicate information to visitors. The site uses navigational data.

**Use and Disclosure Information**  
Except as otherwise stated, we may use your information to improve the content of our site, to customize the site to your preferences, to communicate information to you (if you have requested it), for our marketing and research purposes, and for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy.

If you provide personally identifiable information to this site, we may combine such information with other actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection. We will take reasonable measures to prevent personally identifiable information from being combined with passively collected information, unless you consent otherwise. We may disclose your personally identifiable information to other DURECT affiliates worldwide that agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition, we may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties, located in the United States and/or any other country, but only (i) to contractors we use to support our business (e.g., fulfillment services, technical support, delivery services, and financial institutions), in which case we will require such third parties to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy; (ii) in connection with the sale, assignment or other transfer of the business of this site to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy; or (iii) where required by applicable laws, court order, or government regulations.

In addition, we will make full use of all information acquired through this site that is not in personally identifiable form.

**Access and Correction**  
To keep your personally identifiable information accurate, current and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update our correct personally identifiable information in our possession that you have previously submitted via this site.

**Security**  
We take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your computer to our site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.

**Links to Other Web Sites**  
This site may contain links to other Web sites. Please be aware that we do not control other Web sites and that, in any case, this Privacy Policy does not apply to those Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every Web site you visit.

**Other Terms**  
Your use of this site is subject to our Legal Notice.

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices on this site, please contact us as follows:

DURECT Corporation  
2 Results Way  
Cupertino, CA 95014 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 2, 2002.

Back to top
